I love you.
Chain of vision, start and come
Oh, Nareff, I shall savor killing you.
To avenge my dear son, I shall rip
out your insides while you watch.
And I can't let him find Whole Horse's
body or else my chance will be lost.
She's not behind the counter, either.
It'll be even worse if
the other three show up.
I need to kill them one by one, dammit.
Stay back. Go away.
Oh, Madame, are you here?
I thought I heard some
kind of crash back here.
Are you okay?
I'm coming in, Madame.
Oh, no! What happened?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's only a tiny fall.
Just bruised my hip a little bit.
You fell down?
You can't be falling now.
And you burned your left hand?
You're being much, much too careless.
Oh, thank you, dear boy.
I'm fine.
No problem, I promise.
Who said you could come in here, damn it!
I'll spare you my wrath for
now, but when the time is right,
I'll kill you just like I
killed that bastard whole horse.
All it takes is just a tiny little wound,
and then you're finished I'll turn you
into my very own puppet of justice?
Cool here your staff!
Madame you seem to be
sweating a lot. It's nothing.
Don't concern yourself with me.
I'm fine Just go to your room and
get some rest Well, if you insist.
So, I was wondering, are you running
the entire hotel all by yourself?
Don't you have some family around to help?
Like a son?
I've gotten used to living alone.
Ah, I see.
Sounds lonely to me.
Just think, life with a
son and daughter-in-law.
Your grandkids could run
around and play in the lobby.
They'd definitely cheer this place up.
It'd be a little noisy, but
that's what makes families great!
If you had a son, he'd probably
be older than me, right?
Hey, what's the matter?
Did you have a son who
moved away or something?
No, he passed away.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
That was terribly insensitive of me.
You're the one who
killed him, you monster.
I despise you.
I'll slaughter you.
Please sit down.
I was still just a kid.
Isn't this great?
Ah, the memories.
Tonight you can think about me
as if I'm your own beloved son
Ask me for anything, okay?
You rotten little brat!
I should just kill you
right now, you fool!
Wow, your living alone has
been pretty tough on you
Huh?
What's that guy doing there?
This Card must have made his stand vanish
as soon as it shot the bullet
into his mouth! Gah! What?
No, that face!
Hey!
Look behind you, Paula Raff!
Behind you, you fool!
No way!
You're whole horse!
What are you doing?
Getting my vengeance!
I'm the mother of Cenderfold who you
mercilessly murdered in cold blood!
Chariot!
So you're a stand-user all along!
Dare play a part in murdering my boy
and I'll make sure you pay for it!
Mr.
Joestar, I need help!
It's too late.
I'm afraid your trusty friends will
never hear your cries, my dear.
Because...
I've summoned my own allies.
Who the hell are you guys?
Wait, it's you!
But you're dead!
You were dead when we got here!
You're the one from India!
Holy shit, we've got zombies!
Behold the terrifying
power of justice, my stand!
One can only have one stand,
But Justice the Fog Stand can transform
the dead into my personal army!
It can control hundreds of
corpses, even thousands of them!
She'll turn you into a personal puppet!
I need only to give you a little scratch.
It doesn't take much, you know.
Soon you'll be mine.
Then my Stand Justice will
take care of the rest!
You're dead! Yahoo!
I'm out of here!
Ah, ah, ah, Polnareff!
Don't I save you.
You're on your own, pal.
You can't escape my righteous
vengeance, Polnareff!
I'll yank your brains out
through your nostrils!
I'll snap your spine in
half and shatter your bones!
I'll crush your balls till they pop!
My vengeance comes now!
I couldn't possibly run so fast!
Take this!
Dammit!
That filthy coward ran into the back room!
After him, you fools!
Break down that door at once!
Mare, just my luck.
This hallway leads down to the basement.
I'm so far away from them now. Mr.
Joestar and the others will never hear me.
I don't think those creepy
zombies can beat me,
but if I get even a single
scratch, I'll be in trouble.
She'll take control of
me just like Hall Horse.
Damn it!
Isn't there any way outside?
And of course the windows
have iron bars on them.
Damn it!
I just have to keep these freaks as
far away from my skin as possible.
And now they're coming down the hallway.
They must be checking every room. Damn it.
They're getting closer and closer.
Wait a minute. Oh, come on.
Did I run into another bathroom?
Why am I always getting
ambushed in bathrooms?
Damn it.
The toilet is so dirty.
All right, just try it.
But the second you walk in, my chariot will
chop up four of you in a single breath.
What's going on?
Now it's totally quiet out there. Creepy.
Damn zombie.
That old hag what the hell are they doing
aren't they going to break down the door?
What's taking them so long
come on do something damn it!
Perfect!
You've finally fallen under my justice's
control, you shitty little brat!
And now, if you don't open that door
and come out on your own this second,
I'm going to slowly crush your face
and pull you through the keyhole!
Laugh now!
How pitiful, Polnareff.
Very pitiful, indeed.
This isn't even close to the level of
torture you put my centerfold through.
Because of your cowardice, my precious
son died in unimaginable agony.
Now then, how about we have
you clean the bathroom, eh?
Sound like a plan to you?
Lick the toilet until
it sparkles like noob.
Don't be shy.
Lick it till it's shiny, like this.
No, not that!
I'm not anything but that!
Oh, God, help me!
Oh, you startled me.
You must learn to knock, my young man.
What can I do for you?
I'm here looking for
Polnareff, and I did knock.
Maybe you didn't hear me because you
were too busy doing something else.
I wonder what.
I'm looking for Polnareff,
but I can't find him.
Seen him, Grandma?
Hmm, damn.
Now what?
Unlike Polnareff,
this Jotaro is clever and knows the right
questions to ask to get what he wants.
I have to be careful.
Playing dumb will just
make him more suspicious.
I need something else.
What a troublesome brat.
I know.
I'll tell him where he can find Polnareff,
and as soon as he turns his back, I'll
turn him into a pincushion with these.
Then he'll be easy
pickings for my justice.
Yes, of course I can help you.
I know exactly where he is, Mr. Jotaro.
He and I were just
having a lovely chat. Oh.
This isn't good.
Jotaro has no idea.
A tiny scratch will spell his doom.
Stay back. Tell Mr.
Joestar and Kakyoin that hag is the enemy.
He's in the bathroom, but he's
been in there for quite some time.
Of course he's taking a shit.
Through this door here?
Yes, that's right.
Once you're through the
door, make a left turn.
The bathroom is at the
very end of the hall.
What an incompetent fool!
You are a child after all!
Murdering Polnareff will
delight my son's soul!
And spilling your blood, Jotaro, will
send Lord Dio in Egypt into jubilation!
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
You have a second?
I got a question.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Did you trip or were you just that clumsy?
You should be more careful.
That was too close.
Yeah, could have been real bad.
It could have gone into your eye or cut
a huge chunk out of your scrawny neck.
You're pretty damn lucky.
Sorry to ask before you even get
up, but I have a few more questions
First on the list, how did
you know my name is Jotaro?
I never told you my name.
No one has, not since we got here.
I find that strange.
Well, come on, tell me.
You know, it's funny.
Maybe it's because I
watched Columbo as a kid.
But it's little details like
that that keep me up at night.
Oh, you're beginning to hurt
this old lady's feelings.
It's the guest book.
You wrote your name in
the guest book earlier.
Don't tell me you don't remember.
It's so dry.
You wrote Jotaro Kujo, yes.
Oh, then I guess you mean
this guest book here?
Yes, that's it.
See, your name is right here.
Jotaro Kujo?
Jotaro isn't ridden
anywhere in this old thing.
Calling me Joestar when we first
met was your first mistake.
I've suspected you since.
I told the others not to use my name.
And yet, you know it.
Which could only mean...
Cut the crap, you old hag!
I already know you're one of
the stand users that's after us.
The jig is up.
What's the matter now?
Aren't you going to show
me your stand and fight?
You're looking right at it!
Oh, God!
My stand justice always prevails!
All it needs is one small scratch, and
then your life is as good as forfeit.
You've fallen into my trap, Jotaro!
Pull the riff!
Jotaro, it's me, Haw Horse, remember?
And Yaba's stand is made
entirely out of fog!
It'll split your wound right open
and start flowing through your body.
That's how she controls you with it.
It'll even control corpses!
Shut your mouth, whole horse!
Can you punch the fog with your fist?
Or cut the fog with your sword?
Or shoot it with a gun?
I don't think so.
Absolutely futile!
There's nothing you can
do but accept your fate!
It's the biggest, toughest,
fiercest stand there is!
Ours are puny, by comparison.
We're no match for it.
Nothing stands a chance
against justice. Lovely.
Keep it coming, whole horse.
Your fearful praise is music to my ears.
Now I'll control you too, Jotaro.
Quick, run away, Jotaro.
She's gonna turn you into a puppet.
Good grief.
I don't need to run.
Before that old hag takes another breath,
I'll defeat that stand and send
her back in. Huh? What was that?
I could have sworn you just made some
idiotic proclamation about defeating me,
you little brat.
Before I take another
breath, is that right?
Well, I'll do that.
I'll do that right.
What did you do to me?
Totoro's star platinum is
sucking in her entire stand!
No!
No, please stop!
I can't breathe!
And he's holding it in!
He's suffocating that bitch!
Hmph, you see that?
Looks like her head is in a bit of a fog.
You ask me, that's justice at its finest.
I'm so angry!
What do you mean, what
have I been licking?
You ask such stupid questions.
I honestly don't see why that matters.
The toilet.
You were licking what again?
I couldn't hear you very well.
Who cares what it was?
Now I need to disinfect my tongue, okay?
Give me the medicine already!
I thought I just heard the word toilet.
What are you giggling about?
Actually, I already knew about that,
but I couldn't resist picking
on him about this first.
Hold on!
Jotaro already told you
what happened, didn't he?
You shitty old man!
You were just messing with me!
Forget the medicine!
All right, all right, I'm sorry.
Come here and I'll fix you up, Polnareff.
If you don't take care of
that, it'll get infected.
Ahem!
Toilet.
You licked it real good.
Jojaro, cocky-wee!
Come on, let's just get
the hell out of here.
Everyone, come outside. Huh?
What on earth?
We step outside of the
hotel and this place is a...
It's a graveyard.
She was using her stand's fog to make this
graveyard look like a town and a hotel.
So the whole time we were here, we were
talking to some corpses six feet under?
You wanna take her with us?
Are you serious?
Sure am.
We need to know how many more
Stan users are out there?
What their powers are?
And wherever Dio's dug a
hole for himself in Egypt?
as well as what his power is.
If we get the hag to tell us, it might
finally give us the edge that we need.
That's worth the risk
of dragging her around.
I highly doubt she'll be willing
to share that information, though.
We just need to use my hermit, Purple.
I'll project everything she's
thinking onto a TV screen.
Great idea.
We'll hop over to the next
town and use a TV there.
Hull horse, you slide
ball! That's our car!
Sorry, boys.
I'm sticking with Dio after all.
Catch y 'all later.
Provided you all don't
die before then, that is.
A little advice for y 'all.
You better put a bullet between
that old lady's eyes real
soon or else you'll find out just
how terrifying Dio really is!
And you do not want that!
Hm?
See ya!
Does anyone know what he's talking about?
Cause I don't!
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got the money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Foreign types with a hookah. I say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves, oh-hey-oh.
You drop your drink,
then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
Why are you here?
What could you want with me?
Lord Dio truly trusts no one.
He should be able to become smaller.
When I say I'm gonna do something...
He went flying like the other guy.
Oh my god!
Power isn't necessary if all you
want to do is kill your opponent.